I have heard that dark souls is supposed to be a really hard game.
But is it harder than being a single parent working three jobs to support ungrateful children?
Y-yeah, probably.
This game has been very requested, but I've never actually played it, because I assumed it was a Call of Duty ripoff.
Like many other games, first we get to create our own character. First, we get to name him.
Uhrm... Can pen book?
Then we get to pick his class.
I don't know, I'm thinking Cleric because that's like a priest.
That means it's the only class with an actual university degree.
But, maybe not the best at fighting monsters.
"Wanderer"? If someone calls himself a wanderer he's obviously a douchebag.
Thief? Thi-- really, Thief!?
Well, I'm sorry, but what's he gonna do? Walk up to a two-story demon and sell him an unlocked iPhone!?
Uh, this is the only one I can't actually find anything wrong with.
Then, we get to decide what our character looks like. He will be wearing a helmet the entire time, but it's important for his self-confidence.
Backstory intro! It's like five minutes long. I think I can do it faster.
So, like, forever ago, there was nothing but white trees and immortal dragons.
One of the Dragons fell asleep with a cigarette and thus fire was created.
And with fire came life, and with life came Souls.
There were, like, super Souls called "Lord Souls", which gained superpowers to a select few individuals.
They were given to, in order:
Nito, he is... yeah, that's, that's Death. That's obviously the Grim Reaper. Do I even need to tell you that?
The second one was the Witch of Izalith.
The third one was the Sun God Gwyn. Yes, I know he looks somewhat generic, but he is really important.
Please, remember him. I will not remind you later.
I don't remember the fourth one, I think it was Michael, the Convenience Store Owner, so I'm going with that.
The lords were like, "Dragons are stupid, let's kick their asses!"
A dragon named Seath revealed the other dragons' weakness and betrayed them, because he was very insecure about his looks.
And that is why you say no to bullies.
Gwyn threw what he called "Sunlight Bolts" at them. Obviously that's lightning, but names are important for building a brand.
It peeled their scales off, so the dragons weren't immortal anymore. So they were pretty shitty at this whole "immortality" thing.
Then Nito swooped in and took their lives. He, uh, did his job and expected to get praised for it.
The Witch of Izalith did fuck all and Michael refused to refill the slush machine.
Dragons are dead and now the age of fire has begun. Yay, the lords!
But late that afternoon, the first flames have started to go out. And if they disappear completely, the people with Lord Souls will die.
Except for Michael, he has a Dark Soul or something. He's the first human, I don't get it.
Then a bunch of other shit happens and there are now people that can't die, called the "Undead".
And you are one of them. Congratulations!
Eventually, Undead people lose their minds. They become insane because they live for so long.
So they locked him up in a place called the Undead Asylum. And there you are. Welcome.
Did you have any problem understanding all that? Good. You and everyone else.
We are running around semi-naked in this prison, then we face the first boss.
He's not very hard, but it does take time. Then we walk up some stairs and meet Oscar.
"Oh, hello. I'm done for, I'm afraid. But before I lose my sanity, I wish to ask something of you. Will you help me?
"Take out my laptop, open Firefox and remove EVERYTHING."
Get health potions and the key out. Then a giant crow shows up and carries you to this place.
Want an explanation? Well, change game!
This guy tells you:
"I don't know you. I've never met you before."
"But you do look like the kind of guy that wants to ring two church bells."
"N-n-not that I want you to do that or anything, b-b-baka!"
So, you're off to ring two church bells.
The first bell is in Undead Burg, a city for the undead. It's a very boring place.
It's kinda...
It's kinda... DEAD!
Aaaaaah! (☞ ▀ ͜͞ʖ▀)☞
The second boss is a bull demon, and after defeating him, I realized that I haven't lost any health so far.
But Dark Souls was supposed to be hard!
When I was facing the third boss, the gargoyles, I didn't see any gargoyles.
I saw statistics, graphs, equations!
As I was ringing the bell, I realized I am a Dark Souls prodigy. A natural. And I will dance my way through--
This is fucking bullshit! This is fucking stupid! Fuck everything!
The Capra Demon is somewhat hard. It took me four tries until I searched for a youtube guide.
Eventually, you reach the second bell's location, a place called "Blighttown".
This part is really annoying, because the enemies have this special ability called "framerate issues".
Yes, I know you can download dsfix, but I want to play the game the way it was intended.
I am about to fight a boss that apparently drops a great chest.
Oh, oh, I get it. I-I got the joke. Great chest ahead, I got it.
Destroy her, ring bell.
Now the gates to a fortress called "Sen's Fortress" are open.
A lot of people consider this the best part of the game, and a lot of people are completely WRONG!
After you defeat the boss at the top, these fellows take you and carry you over the wall.
Welcome to Anor Londo. It's a city built by the sun-god Gwyn. The guy from the intro.
It used to be very populated, but then they started outsourcing jobs to China, and now it's pretty much abandoned.
At least that's what they say, but wouldn't you say it's a bit clean? I need answers, dammit!
You travel through it and face Smough and Ornstein.
I *think* these bosses are hard, but walking through the city was so hard I got a cerebral aneurysm, and now my brain can't render difficulty.
After they are defeated, you meet this woman.
"Hello, I'm the daughter of Gwyn, the god from the intro."
"First flames are going out and you're going to sacrifice yourself to keep them going."
"And you're going to do what I say. Men always do what I say, for some non-apparent reason."
After she's done talking to you, you can join her covenant.
Now, this would be a pretty terrible review if I didn't explain what covenants were.
To get to the first flames, you have to traverse New Londo.
Why does it look like a water park?
This guy tells you that it was to trap these four kings, that are so powerful that if they got out, they would be a threat to our very existence.
But I'm gonna drain the place, because I want to know their side of the story!
And they attacked me for no reason.
I think I just saved the planet.
This is Kaathe. He is a... uh... yeah...
Anyways, he says:
"What's up, motherfucker? Listen."
"Okay, me and a bunch of my bros, we want the first flame to go out because, then the age of dark begins."
"Sounds totally metal, amirite?"
"But lord Gwyn, you know, the fucking god guy from the intro, he's like, he stops it because he's a dick."
"So listen, if you go down there with a fire extinguisher, then I'll make you Dark Lord."
"It would be like tha-that thing, tha--- the movie with the fucking ball in space."
Maybe I have to explain this.
As the first flames were going out, the guy from the intro thought: "Maybe if I stay down there and blow on it it will
survive."
So he locked himself into a room with the Fire, bringing only a copy of Dark Souls on the PS3 and an adult magazine.
Eventually, that drove him crazy and he became the Lord of cinder.
Now we've got to get to him to give him an ass-whooping. But the door leading to the fire is locked.
We need the Lord Souls from the other lords (minus Michael) to get in.
Okay, so we have a dragon that doesn't have scales, and it turns out scales are what makes dragons immortal.
To avoid awkward conversations, he decided to research scales.
Drove him completely crazy. Look at all these books!
E-readers, motherfucker, have you heard of them!?
Anyways, after he betrayed the dragons, he also stole a crystal that made him immortal.
Then he dies after we hit his tentacle a couple of times. Seriously, do these dragons not have dictionaries?
So, one day she thought to herself, "Hey, first flames were pretty cool, created life and shit. Imma start my own first flames!"
Everyone said it was a terrible idea. She did it anyway.
She started the flames and lost control. The flames turned her city into hell.
Oops!
It did create life though. Eh, demons.
Then the flames destroyed her family and turned her into a tree.
Oop-- wait, what?
So, she's pretty stupid, and so is this boss fight.
Next soul.
Holy shit, we're about to fight death himself.
I mean, we have faced demons, and kings, and ancient warriors, and even a tree, but this is the first time we will face an actual god.
I have no idea what to expect.
"Greetings and Welcome, Undead.
I have waited for you. Now, are you ready..."
"FOR THY DRIVING EXAM!?"
Alright, we're here, just sitting in the car.
I want you to show me you can get far!
Step on the gas!
Do you know why we stopped the car again?
That's because you just got your license!
We are finally ready to defeat the god of intros.
We walk through a place that could really use a chimney sweep and then we face Gwyn.
Not hard, just takes time.
You get to decide between two endings: become Dark Lord, or kill yourself.
Now, I didn't get to decide. I just saw a bonfire and decided to light it, and apparently I died, and the game ended, and then started again.
New game+, baby.
But I'm not gonna play through that. Bosses take way too long.
So, what else is there to do?
Well, there's the DLC, where you get to face Michael in his convenience store, and then there's PvP.
And you.
You know who you are.
You can go fuck yourself.
Even though I'm too lazy to replay the game, I kind of like Dark Souls.
If you're interested in more Dark Souls story, you should probably check out another channel. And that is the Kilian Experience.
Hi you guys, did you like the video? Why not like it and then share it to everyone?
But, listen. I just doubled subscribers since my last video. What the actual fuck?
But, thanks for 1000 subs.
And you already know what the next video is going to be: Assassin's Creed 2!